algebrahelp.com 2002-12-08

# Algebra.help -- Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement for algebra.help

Privacy Statement

Algebra.Help has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: algebra.help. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. This site also uses cookies to track your path through the site, and return visits. 

Our site's newsletter subscription form reqequests users to give us contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (occupation, age, and education). We use customer contact information from the subscription form to send the user our newsletter when we update our website. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. **algebra.help** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our feedback form asks visitors for contact information (like their email address), and demographic information (like how they found our website). The e-mail address is only used to respond to the user's questions or comments. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.

## Burst! Survey

Our front page links to a survey page. This survey is created and managed by Burst!, our 3rd party advertising company. This survey is voluntary. For Burst!'s privacy statement visit their website at [burstnet.com](http://www.burstnet.com/)

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. Visit our [newsletter page](http://algebrahelp.listbot.com/) to unsubscribe from our newsletter. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can Contact [Burst!](http://www.burstnet.com/) or [ListBot.com](http://www.listbot.com/) if you filled out their respective surveys.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Algebra.Help jrmski @ algebrahelp.com

You may also contact us through our feedback page.
